truthforlife.org 2009-06-20

# Truth For Life: Privacy Policy

Truth for Life has created this Privacy Policy to explain why we collect particular information and how we will protect your personal privacy within our Web site. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the Web site located at the URL www.truthforlife.org and any related subdomains.

In order to fully understand your rights we encourage you to read this Privacy Policy. Truth for Life reserves the right at any time and without notice to change this Privacy Policy simply by posting such changes on our Site. Any such change will be effective immediately upon posting.

Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, this Privacy Policy notifies you of; 

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours is collected through the Site; 
  2. Who collects such information; 
  3. How such information is used; 
  4. With whom your information may be shared; 
  5. What choices you have regarding collection, use and distribution of your information; 
  6. What kind of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control; 
  7. and, How you can correct any inaccuracies in your information. 

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to Truth for Life by sending an email to [letters@truthforlife.org](mailto:letters@truthforlife.org "E-mail letters@truthforlife.org"). Please reference this Privacy Policy in your subject line.

 **What Information We Collect and How We Use That Information** : 

The information that we collect relates directly to the action being completed. Depending on the action, we may collect your name, email address, email format preference (HTML vs. Text), address, interests, and similar information. For financial transactions such as donations or store purchases, we will need to collect your credit card number. We use customer information collected to send the requested information, complete the requested transaction, and present the most relevant information to our listeners based on their interests. We never sell, share or trade any of our customer information with other companies.

Any transaction that can be completed online may also be completed via phone or mail, should you have concerns about security. Please see our contact page for information on reaching our customer service team.

 **Contact and Profile Information:** : 

Truth for Life is the sole owner of the information collected on the website. This site does not collect personally identifying information about users except when you specifically and knowingly provide it. For example, we collect information from you in the following ways: 

  * Some areas of our Site request or require contact and other information.
  * During the registration process, we collect personal and other information such as your name, address, and email address.
  * Demographic, interest, and profile data (e.g. gender, what stations you listen to, etc.) may also be collected at our Site.

 **Security**

All information provided to Truth for Life is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us. We are compliant with the strictest industry standards for credit card security and processing, and our team regularly evaluates our systems and processes for additional safeguards.

Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. While we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of such information. To increase the security of your transactions, please protect your usernames and passwords, be sure to log-out of the site when completing your transaction, and use a secure Internet connection when completing a financial transaction. 

**Choice/OptOut:**

Truth for Life provides users with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at any time. Truth for Life gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications. 

  * You can email us at [letters@truthforlife.org](mailto:letters@truthforlife.org "E-mail letters@truthforlife.org")
  * You can click on the "Unsubscribe" link included at the bottom of your email and follow the instructions on the web page. You may choose to opt-out of particular email newsletters or all email communication from Truth For Life. 

**Surveys:**

We may conduct occasional online surveys via our website or via an email newsletter. These surveys are entirely voluntary and you may easily decline to participate.

 **Contacting the Web Site:**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, please contact us by email at [letters@truthforlife.org](mailto:letters@truthforlife.org "E-mail letters@truthforlife.org") or write us at: 

**Mailing Address**

P.O. Box 398000  
Cleveland, OH 44139-8000
